Guide to the Professor John Lienhard Papers
University of Houston Libraries
- Textbooks
  - A Heat Transfer Textbook
    - Draft: Chapter II, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Draft: Chapter III, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Draft: Chapter IV, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Draft: Chapter V, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Draft: Chapter VI Figures, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Draft: Chapter VII, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Draft: Chapter VIII, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Draft: Chapter IX, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Draft: Chapter X, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Draft: Chapter XI, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Draft: Chapter I, Summer 1979 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Draft: Chapter II, Summer 1978 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Draft: Chapter III, Summer 1979 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Draft: Chapter IV, Summer 1979 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Draft: Chapter V, Summer 1979 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Draft: Chapter VI, Summer 1979 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Draft: Chapter VII, Summer 1979 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Draft: Chapter VIII, Summer 1979 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Draft: Chapter IX, Summer 1979 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Draft: Chapter X, Summer 1979 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Draft: Chapter XI, Summer 1979 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Draft: Appendix A, Summer 1979 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Draft: Appendiz B, Summer 1979 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Semifinal Draft: Chapter I, Spring 1979 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Semifinal Draft: Chapter II, Spring 1979 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - Semifinal Draft: Chapter III, Spring 1979 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Semifinal Draft: Chapter IV, Spring 1979 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - Semifinal Draft: Chapter V, Spring 1979 (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - Semifinal Draft: Chapter VI, Spring 1979 (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - Semifinal Draft: Chapter VII, Spring 1979 (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - Semifinal Draft: Chapter VIII, Spring 1979 (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - Semifinal Draft: Chapter IX, Spring 1979 (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - Semifinal Draft: Chapter X, Spring 1979 (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - Semifinal Draft: Chapter XI, Spring 1979 (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - Semifinal Draft: Appendix A, Spring 1979 (Box 13, Folder 50)
    - Draft: Chapter I, Fall 1979 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Draft: Chapter II, Fall 1979 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Draft: Chapter III, Fall 1979 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Draft: Chapter IV, Fall 1979 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Draft: Chapter V, Fall 1979 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Draft: Chapter VI, Fall 1979 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Draft: Chapter VII, Fall 1979 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Draft: Chapter VIII, Fall 1979 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Draft: Chapter IX, Fall 1979 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Draft: Chapter X, Fall 1979 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Draft: Chapter XI, Fall 1979 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Draft: Appendix A, Fall 1979 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Draft: Appendix B, Fall 1979 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Draft: Table of Contents, Chapter I, Fall 1979 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Draft: Chapter II, Fall 1979 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Draft: Chapter III, Fall 1979 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Draft: Chapter IV, Fall 1979 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Draft: Chapter V, Fall 1979 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Draft: Chapter VI, Fall 1979 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Draft: Chapter VII, Fall 1979 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Draft: Chapter VIII, Fall 1979 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Draft: Chapter IX, Fall 1979 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Draft: Chapter X, Fall 1979 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Draft: Chapter XI, Fall 1979 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Draft: Appendix A, Fall 1979 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Draft: Chapter I, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Draft: Chapter II, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Draft: Chapter III, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Draft: Chapter IV, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Draft: Chapter V, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Draft: Chapter VI, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Draft: Chapter VII, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Draft: Chapter VIII, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Draft: Chapter IX, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Draft: Chapter X, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Draft: Chapter X, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Draft: Chapter XI, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Draft: Appendix A, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Draft: Appendix B, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Draft: Title Page, Contents, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - Draft: Preface, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - Draft: Instructor's Supplement 2nd Printing, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - Draft: Chapter XII, Spring 1986 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Draft: Title Page & Contents Page, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Draft: Index11987 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Draft: Chapter 1, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Draft: Chapter 2, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Draft: Chapter 3, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Draft: Chapter 3, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Draft: Chapter 4, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Draft: Chapter 5, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Draft: Chapter 6, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Draft: Chapter 7, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Draft: Chapter 8, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Draft: Chapter 9, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Draft: Chapter 10, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Draft: Chapter 11, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Draft: Chapter 12, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Draft: Appendix A, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Draft: Chapter I (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Draft: Chapter II (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Draft: Chapter III (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Draft: Chapter IV (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Draft: Chapter V (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Draft: Chapter VII (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Draft: Chapter VIII (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Draft: Chapter IX (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Draft: Chapter X (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Draft: Chapter XI (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Draft: Appendix A (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Draft: Chapter I (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Draft: Chapter II (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Draft: Chapter III (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Draft: Chapter IV (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Draft: Chapter V (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Draft: Chapter VI (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Draft: Chapter VII (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Draft: Chapter VIII (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Draft: Chapter IX (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Draft: Chapter X (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Draft: Chapter XI (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Draft: Chapter XII (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Draft: Chapter XII Problems (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Solution Manual: Chapter 1, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Solution Manual: Chapter 2, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Solution Manual: Chapter 3, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Solution Manual: Chapter 4, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - Solution Manual: Chapter 5, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - Solution Manual: Chapter 6, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Solution Manual: Chapter 7, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - Solution Manual: Chapter 8, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - Solution Manual: Chapter 9, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Solution Manual: Chapter 10, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Solution Manual: Chapter 11, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Solution Manual: Chapter 12, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Solution Manual: Index, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Solution Manual: Appendix A, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Page Proofs: Chapter 1 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Page Proofs: Chapter 2,3 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Page Proofs: Chapter 4,5 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Page Proofs: Chapter 6 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Page Proofs: Chapter 7,8 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Page Proofs: Chapter 9 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Page Proofs: Chapter 10 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Page Proofs: Chapter 11 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Page Proofs: Appendix (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Page Proofs Updated: Master Set - Chapter 1 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Page Proofs Updated: Master Set - Chapter 2 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Page Proofs Updated: Master Set - Chapter 3 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Page Proofs Updated: Master Set - Chapter 4 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Page Proofs Updated: Master Set - Chapter 5 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Page Proofs Updated: Master Set - Chapter 6 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Page Proofs Updated: Master Set - Chapter 7 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Page Proofs Updated: Master Set - Chapter 8 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Page Proofs Updated: Master Set - Chapter 9 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Page Proofs Updated: Master Set - Chapter 10 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Page Proofs Updated: Master Set - Chapter 11 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Page Proofs Updated: Master Set - Appendix (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Galley Proofs: Chapter 1, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Galley Proofs: Chapter 2, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Galley Proofs: Chapter 3, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Galley Proofs: Chapter 4, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Galley Proofs: Chapter 5, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Galley Proofs: Chapter 6, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Galley Proofs: Chapter 7, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Galley Proofs: Chapter 8, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Galley Proofs: Chapter 9, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Galley Proofs: Chapter 10, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Galley Proofs: Chapter 11, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Galley Proofs: Chapter 12, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Galley Proofs: Appendix A, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Galley Proofs: Appendix A, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Galley Proofs: Appendix B, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Galley Proofs: Appendix C, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Galley Proofs: End Papers, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous: Correspondence, Prentice Hall, 5/80-11/86 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous: Correspondence, Sean, 9/12/85-5/5/86 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous: Correspondence, 8/85 - 2/87 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous: Errata for Third and Fourth Printings (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous: Materials (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous: Appendix C Nomenclature (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous: Articles, 1922-1975 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous: Book: The Engines of Our Ingenuity (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous: Book: The Engines of Our Ingenuity Ch 9- notes (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous: 1966-1967, 96-97 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Miscellaneous: Errata for 2nd Printing, 8/28/90 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous: Chapter 2 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous: Chapter 2 Art (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous: Chapter 3 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous: Chapter 4 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous: Artwork (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Miscellaneous: Correspondence-Heat Transfer Text, 11/20/90 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Inventing Modern
    - First Proofs - Preface, Chapter 1 & 2, 3/19/03 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - First Proofs - Chapter 3, 4, 5, 3/19/03 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - First Proofs -Chapter 6, 7, 8, 3/19/03 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - First Proofs -Chapter 9, 10, 3/19/03 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - First Proofs -Chapter 11, 12, 13, 3/19/03 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - First Proofs -Chapter 14, 15, 3/19/03 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - First Proofs -Chapter 16, Notes, Index, 3/19/03 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Inventing Modern -Front and Back Cover, 3/19/03 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Inventing Modern Correspondence (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - How Invention Begins
    - How Invention Begins - Book Cover and Blurbs (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - How Invention Begins - First Proofs (1 of 3), 2/17/06 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - How Invention Begins - First Proofs (2 of 3), 2/17/06 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - How Invention Begins - First Proofs (3 of 3), 2/17/06 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - How Invention Begins - Uncorrected Advance Reading Copy (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Alcuin of York - Music Sheet (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Ghosts in the Books - Engines of Our Ingenuity, CD Cover (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - The Phases of Eve/Gilgamesh - CD 2004 (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Online Library Catalog - Finding Aids (Sound Recordings) (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence
    - Correspondence, 1974 -79 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1980 -83 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence To: Lienhard (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence From: Lienhard, 1966- 1990 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Unprocessed materials
  ~20 linear feet